[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following spells in the card game Magic: The Gatheringcan destroy both creatures and enchantments?", "correct_answer": "Mortify", "incorrect_answers": ["Blaze", "Wrath of God", "Putrefy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who portrays Larry, Fletchs research assistant at the newspaper in the movie Fletch?", "correct_answer": "Geena Davis", "incorrect_answers": ["Julia Roberts", "Brad Pitt", "Kevin Bacon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Because of the substance present in these structures of the human body, they can be preserved for centuries avoiding decomposition.", "correct_answer": "Teeth", "incorrect_answers": ["Nails", "Eyelashes", "Eyeballs"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the average weight of an adult nutria?", "correct_answer": "10-20 lbs.", "incorrect_answers": ["15-25 lbs.", "5-10 lbs.", "Over 30 lbs."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did the movie Fast Times at Ridgemont High premiere?", "correct_answer": "1982", "incorrect_answers": ["1984", "1981", "1983"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "At the end of the movie Malone, Jo Barlow, who was infatuated with Malone, reminded him that in five years she would be five years older. Burt Reynolds character replied, So will I.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is not a type of vehicle considered to be in the movie Transformers?", "correct_answer": "747", "incorrect_answers": ["Fighter Jet", "Ambulance", "Aircraft Carrier"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "If the world were a village of 100 people, how many would be illiterate?", "correct_answer": "70", "incorrect_answers": ["50", "40", "60"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the term apex predator which is related to carnivorous animals?", "correct_answer": "A predator that has no predators itself.", "incorrect_answers": ["A very skilled predator that is highly specialized in killing animals.", "It is a term for a human being.", "An animal which consumes the highest number of animal species."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The ghost of this mobster is said to haunt two locations. One of them is a hotel in Las Vegas, the other - a private residence in Beverly Hills.", "correct_answer": "Bugsy Siegel", "incorrect_answers": ["John Gotti", "Al Capone", "Frank Costello"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "On the Canadian 2 dollar bill, what flag flies over the parliament building?", "correct_answer": "US flag", "incorrect_answers": ["British Flag", "UN flag", "French Flag"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie, The African Queen, the safety valve on the Queens boiler was malfunctioning because there was a screwdriver stuck in it.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]